A Guide to the Fairfax County Road Petitions, 1844-1908
Fairfax Circuit Court Historic Records Center
- Walker, Samuel T. September, 1877 (Box-folder 4: RP-137)
  From point on Hunters Mill Road to William Walter's Mill
- Unnamed December, 1877 (Box-folder 4: RP-138)
  Road from Bull Run to Fox Mill
- Burke, T. T. January, 1878 (Box-folder 4: RP-139)
  Road from the Colchester Road to the Newman Road
- Farnham, David H. January, 1878 (Box-folder 4: RP-140)
  Road from the Falls Road to the Georgetown Pike
- Seaman, C. H. October, 1878 (Box-folder 4: RP-141)
  Little River Turnpike to county road at land of B. F. Shreve
- Wooster, Frank March, 1878 (Box-folder 4: RP-142)
  Little River Turnpike to Orange & Alexandria Railroad at Skinner's Crossing
- Downing, A. J. March, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-143)
  Courthouse road to the Ridge Road
- Ellis, J. R. 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-144)
  Road from county road near Lewis Chapel to Telegraph Station on the Alexandria and Fredericksburg Railroad
- Freeman, A. April, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-145)
  Point of Road leading from Court House and Hunters Mill Road to Vienna near Murnanes's Gate
- Hine, O. E. December, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-146)
  Change: Orcutt Road to point where it intersects with Maple Avenue
- Hirst, John E. November, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-147)
  Road leading from Falkner's Shop on Leesburg Turnpike to Fall's Church
- Machen, James P. January, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-148)
  Change: Old Road over Holmes Run known as Barcroft Bridge
- Miller, Willard N. July, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-149)
  Road leading from Little River Turnpike to Backlick Road by Lebanon school house
- Taylor, A. J. April, 1879 (Box-folder 4: RP-150)
  Great Falls and Lewinsville Road to the Middle Turnpike
- Unnamed July, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-151)
  Ridge Road
- Burke, T. T. May, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-152)
  Yates Ford Road from Clifton Station to Union Mills
- Dorsey, R. B. October, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-153)
  Beginning at corner of the land of Smyth
- Gillingham, W. April, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-154)
  Road from Gum Spring to the intersection with the Mount Vernon Lane
- Lee, E. W. April, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-155)
  Road leading from Annandale to Springfield to the Little River Turnpike
- Moore, W. E. October, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-156)
  Change: Orcutt Road
- Powell, John 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-157)
  Change: Ridge Road from Alexandria Turnpike to Herndon Station
- Smith, Francis M. September, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-158)
  Road from the Old Union school house to the Alexandria Pike
- Stalcup, Samuel S. 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-159)
  Road from Lincolnville to the Chain Bridge Road
- Taylor, A. J. August, 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-160)
  Road beginning at the Alexandria Turnpike to the Falls Road
- Thompson, Joseph 1880 (Box-folder 4: RP-161)
  Public Highway from Andrew Chapel to Jackson Mill
- Bennett, Hudson March, 1881 (Box-folder 4: RP-162)
  Road from Hasbrook corner to Waples Mill Road
- Dey, Charles W. February, 1881 (Box-folder 4: RP-163)
  Point on the Newman Road to County Road to Herndon
- Harrison, George F. August, 1881 (Box-folder 4: RP-164)
  Road from Little River Turnpike to Centreville and Frying Pan Road
- Skinner, Burdett December, 1881 (Box-folder 4: RP-165)
  Road from Braddock Road to Pohick Road
- Burke, Hannah 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-166)
  Road from Pohick Road through Lee Chapel to Road leading from Burke's Station
- Chambliss, C. W. August, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-167)
  Road from Ridge Road to the Turnpike leading to the city
- Chapman, Thomas F. November, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-168)
  Continue county road to outside gate of Sycamore Farm
- Collins, B. M. May, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-169)
  Change: Road bed of Germantown Road
- Follin, Richard October, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-170)
  Road through land of Thomas Carper and the Rocky Run to Old Union Church
- Fox, W. H. November, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-171)
  Change: Fox's Mill Road from Difficult Bridge to Waple's Mill
- Taylor, A. J. June, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-172)
  Unnamed
- Tebbs, A. Sidney May, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-173)
  Intersection of Herndon and Dranesville Roads to Leesburg Turnpike
- Woodbury, Levi June, 1882 (Box-folder 5: RP-174)
  Change: road leading from Union Mills Road to Clifton
- Carter, Rose July, 1883 (Box-folder 5: RP-175)
  Change: Hunter's Mill Road at the hickory tree corner to Thorton's land
- McPherson, John May, 1883 (Box-folder 5: RP-176)
  Road from McPherson's farm to the Waples Mill Road
- Poole, Joseph L." May, 1883 (Box-folder 5: RP-177)
  Road to take the place of Garner's Mill Road
- Salsbury, H. L. June, 1883 (Box-folder 5: RP-178)
  Road through Salsbury's land
- Woodyard, J. P. July, 1883 (Box-folder 5: RP-179)
  Road from Wolf Run Shoals Road to Ox Road, opposite of Arundel's Tavern
- Coleman, John B. May, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-180)
  Road connecting the Old Leesburg Road to the Leesburg Turnpike
- Davis, F. C. May, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-181)
  Road from the Occoquan Bridge to Elk Horn Branch
- Evans, P. L. July, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-182)
  Road from Telegraph Road to a point on Hooes Road
- Keene, James O. March, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-183)
  Change: Keene Mill Road
- Kincheloe, N. June, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-184)
  Road leading from Centreville to Manassas to Clifton Station
- Mills, L. F. September, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-185)
  Change: "Lemon Road" running from Middle Turnpike to Falls Church and Lewinsville Roads
- Providence District Road Commissioners 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-186)
  Vienna & Andrew Chapel Road
- Roby, Edgar W. April, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-187)
  Road beginning at Little River Turnpike to the Falls Church Road
- Sewall, W. H. November, 1884 (Box-folder 5: RP-188)
  Road from the Blacksmith Shop of Horace Gibson on the Little River Turnpike to Falls Church Road at Mills Crossing Road
- Adams, Ira W. September, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-189)
  Stone's Old Mill Road
- Bennett, Hudson October, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-190)
  Road commencing at Vale...from Fairfax Court House to Dranesville
- Centreville District Road Commissioners April, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-191)
  Change: Road leading from Old Braddock Road to Clifton
- Dey, Charles W. July, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-192)
  Road from C.W. Dey road to Ox Road
- Ford, C. F. June, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-193)
  Change: Road leading from Old Colchester Road to Fairfax Station
- Stuart, William May, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-194)
  Road near the house of John and Thomas Clarke to the Lawyers Road
- Trueax, John B. July, 1885 (Box-folder 5: RP-195)
  Location of Pole Road running from Pool Run to James Hunter's Gate
- Butler, F. L. November, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-196)
  Open portion of New Market Road
- Canfield, B. December, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-197)
  Change: Hunter's Mill Road leading to Lawyers Road
- Dunlop, G. T. February, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-198)
  Road from Herndon Chantilly Road the the Valley Road
- Fisher, Alexander February, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-199)
  Point on Hampton Road at Sandy Run to Hampton Road
- Flagg, Edmund December, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-200)
  Road passing through the Middle Turnpike
- Ford, C. J. November, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-201)
  Change: Road on R. C. Jones' land
- Hine, O. E. October, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-202)
  Change: Road running from Washington, Ohio and Western Railway near Vienna
- Hutchison, M. A. April, 1886 (Box-folder 5: RP-203)
  Road from Lawyers Road to County Road to Herndon
- Jackson, John T. July, 1886 (Box-folder 5:RP-204)
  Road from John Jackson's land to the Gum Spring and Wolcott Road
- Lanham, John March, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-205)
  Road from Alexandria Pike to the Georgetown Pike
- Martin, Georgina 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-206)
  Road from Braddock Road to the land of Georgine Martin
- Philips, E. D. September, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-207)
  County road leading from Old Union Church to Rocky Run
- Sangster, James April, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-208)
  Road from the new road to "Lee Chapel", to Burkes Station, passing through the land of Hannah Burke
- Simpson, E. F. April, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-209)
  Change: "Detwiler Road" from Clifton to Centreville Road
- Simpson, E. F. May, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-210)
  Change: Clifton and Yates Ford Road to avoid a heavy grade
- Simpson, E. F. June, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-211)
  Road through the land of William Harris
- Wooster, Frank Jr. September, 1886 (Box-folder 6: RP-212)
  Road from New Guinea Road to a point on the land of B. Skinner
- Unnamed 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-213)
  Clifton and Centreville
- Averill, W. B. April, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-214)
  Change: Road leading from Old Church Road to the Herndon Road
- Dunn Loring Land & Improvement Company October, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-215)
  Road from point on Backlick Road (Old Gallows Road) to Backlick Road
- Harris, Richard July, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-216)
  Re-open west end of New Market Road
- Harris, James February, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-217)
  Open a road from Charles Thornton's lands to Berks Station
- Leigh, Alfred March, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-218)
  Change: Road leading from Dranesville to Herndon
- Lukens, C. June, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-219)
  Road from the Pole Road in Mount Vernon district to Long Branch Station on the A & F Railroad to Backlick Road
- Mason, B. R. February, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-220)
  Road from the Telegraph Road to Old County Road at John Henderson's Corner
- McClintock, A. August, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-221)
  Road from the Little River Turnpike to the Annandale and Old Tavern Road leading towards Washington
- Murphy, W. October, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-222)
  Change: Willow Spring Road on property of Col. E. White
- November, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-223)
  Unknown
- Snowden, W. H. October, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-224)
  From the farm of W.H. Snowden to the "County road" leading from "Little Hunting Creek" to Accotink and Alexandria Highway
- Thompson, J. C. June, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-225)
  Road from Little River Turnpike to the Braddock Road
- Van Devanter, M. G. November, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-226)
  Road on a point near bridge on Falls Church Road to the Little River Turnpike
- Wright, Robert September, 1887 (Box-folder 6: RP-227)
  Widen the road leading from Jenkin's Corner to Andrew Chapel
- Birch, F. July, 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-228)
  County Road from the middle of Alexandria Pike to Alexandria Line
- Collins, W. G. April, 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-229)
  Point on River Road to the Potomac River
- Hall, John R. October, 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-230)
  Change: Part of County Road known as Colchester Road near Doddridge Lee
- Kincheloe, E. W. 1888 (Box-folder 6" RP-231)
  Road from Braddock Road to Warrenton Pike
- Kirby, Joshua 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-232)
  Road from Lincolnville County Road to East Falls Church Depot
- Lash, James L. 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-233)
  Road from Occoquan to Colchester
- Little River Turnpike Company June, 1888 (Box-folder 7: RP-234)
  Road report on the Little River Turnpike
- Mt. Vernon District Road Commissioners September, 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-235)
  Report on road from Gum Springs to Mt. Vernon
- Pearson, F. W. July, 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-236)
  Road from Vienna to Hunter's Mill, County Road
- Thompson, Daniel 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-237)
  Road from Money's Corner on the Lawyer's Road to Thorton (Wheile) Station
- Wall, James A. 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-238)
  Road from Herndon and Detwiler Road to Dunlop's Gate
- Wells, John T. 1888 (Box-folder 6: RP-239)
  Road from Bull Run to the Turnpike at J. Well's Corner
- Birch, William R. November, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-240)
  Road from Leesburg Pike to Carlin Springs
- Carlin, Edwin 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-241)
  Road extension of Mutersbaugh Road
- Dennison, C. A. October, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-242)
  Road from the Georgetown Road to the road leading from the turnpike to Dunn Loring
- Dewey, Albert A. 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-243)
  Road leading from the Braddock Road to the Guinea Road near Long Branch
- Harris, Joseph 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-244)
  Road from Ball's Ford on Bull Run to Newmarket Road
- Harrison, George F. December, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-245)
  Road from Little River Pike to Ox Road
- Mutersbaugh, John January, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-246)
  Road from the land of John Mutersbaugh to the public road leading from Chain Bridge to Falls Church
- Otis, Mary A. 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-247)
  Change: Road leading from Clifton to the Colchester Road
- Starin, Ahab October, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-248)
  Road from the corner of Ely and Sarner, ending near the Newton Estate
- Terrett, J. W. November, 1889 (Box-folder 7: RP-249)
  Road leading from Episcopal Theological Seminary to Bailey's Crossroads to a post in the line of Terrett
- Ayres, Jonas April, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-250)
  Road from the Braddock Road to the Little River Turnpike
- Evans, P. L. February, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-251)
  Change: the new road from Hooes Road to Telegraph Road to the Telegraph Road
- Fox, William H. November, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-252)
  Change: county road from Waples Mill across the land of A. B. Millard
- Hampton, W. H. October, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-253)
  Road from Elgin's school house to the Yates Ford Road
- Harris, W. H. August, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-254)
  Road commencing at Bull Run...to the Centreville and Manassas Road
- Lee, Philip D. C. August, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-255)
  Widen road near Horse Pen Bridge on the Chantilly and Herndon Road
- Leigh, Alfred, Jr. November, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-256)
  Widen county road where it crosses Difficult Run, near Leigh and Beal's (formerly Jackson's) Mill
- Mount Vernon District Road Commissioners March, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-257)
  Road survey of Accotink Pike
- Pitman, E. M. April, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-258)
  Change: Road at Pitman's Mill for the erection of a bridge over Great Rock Cedar Run
- Staats, P. V. April, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-259)
  Change: road leading from Walter's Mill to Freedom Hill
- Steele, William H. April-May, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-260)
  Change: county road known as the Falls Church Road - from Fairfax Court House to Falls Church
- Stuart, William T. July, 1890 (Box-folder 7: RP-261)
  Change: road from bridge over Difficult Run at Hunter's Mill to Hunter's Mill Store
- Cummings, Moses A. March, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-262)
  Extend Maple Avenue in Vienna to Flint Hill Cemetery
- Dodson, W. W. September, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-263)
  Change: Sawmill Road
- Howard, George T. November, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-264)
  Discontinue portion of Ox Road from the north line of George Howard's land to intersection of county road leading from Frying Pan to Herndon
- Hutchinson, L. E. May, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-265)
  Change: road from Thompson's precinct enters road leading from Little River Turnpike to the Town of Herndon
- Hutchinson, M. B. April, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-266)
  Road commencing at Sanford Hutchinson's corner on Little River Turnpike to Braddock Road
- Rumsey, W. T. October, 1891 (Box-folder 7: RP-267)
  Road from some point on the Little River Turnpike not more than two miles from Court House Building to Falls Church
- Agnew, John P. November, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-268)
  Change: from Mero's store to Gum Spring
- Borden, Daniel L. June, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-269)
  Road from River Road (Garner's Mill Road) to Georgetown and Leesburg Pike
- Bradford, Webster B. May, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-270)
  Open portion of River Road (Garner's Mill Road) from Seneca Road to Loudoun and Fairfax Line
- Gheen, J. R. M. November, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-271)
  Road from at Red Hill to the Braddock Road at Salisbury Farm
- Gillingham, M. August, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-272)
  Colchester Road over Pohick Run
- Hollister, C. K. December, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-273)
  Road leading from the Colchester Road to Payne's Church Road
- Payne, M. M. February, 1892 (Box-folder 8: RP-274)
  Road entering the Court House by the Warrenton and Little River Turnpikes
- Davenport, James L. April, 1893 (Box-folder 8: RP-274)
  Road from West End Catholic Church to the Corporation Limits of the Town of Falls Church
- Elgin, John O. November, 1893 (Box-folder 8: RP-276)
  Beginning in Wolf Run Shoals Road, at the Elgin School House...to Yates Ford Road
- Hollister, C. K. January, 1893 (Box-folder 8: RP-277)
  Road leading from the Colchester Road to Braddock Road
- Kincheloe, W. S. January, 1893 (Box-folder 8: RP-278)
  Extend county road from Woodyard's Precinct...to Ford's Mill Road
- Watts, William W. July, 1893 (Box-folder 8: RP-279)
  Road from Braddock Road near Accotink Run to Little River Turnpike over the old tavern
- Ashton, S. T. August, 1894 (Box-folder 8: RP-280)
  Discontinue portion of county road leading from Centreville to the Little River Turnpike
- Dye, J. F. August, 1894 (Box-folder 8: RP-281)
  At the point on the old county road leading from Burke's Station to Lee Chapel...to a point 15 feet from Railroad land
- Dyer, J. F. April, 1894 (Box-folder 8: RP-281)
  At a point on the old county road leading from Burke's Station to Lee Chapel...to a point 15 feet from Railroad land
- Unnamed November, 1894 (Box-folder 8: RP-282)
  Road from Falls Church to Little River Turnpike
- Dyer, John April, 1895 (Box-folder 8: RP-283)
  Widen Guinea Road near Burke's Station
- Garrett, Benjamin C. March, 1895 (Box-folder 8: RP-284)
  From a point on the road leading from Herndon to the Ox Road...to a point on the road leading from Wiehle to the Lawyer's Road
- Kenyon, Benjamin June, 1895 (Box-folder 8: RP-285)
  Road leading from Freedom Hill to Middle Turnpike...to road from Freedom Hill to Walter's Mill
- Slack, S. J. October, 1895 (Box-folder 8: RP-286)
  County road between the Court House and Ridge Road, beginning at Robert Mateers Lane and ending at a convenient point on Ridge Road
- Woolen, S. J. May, 1895 (Box-folder 8: RP-287)
  Road right of way from Collingwood Beach to the County Road
- Alvord, Henry E. February, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-288)
  Change: Road from Old Union to Georgetown Turnpike, through the lands of Mrs. Carper and others, near Bethel Baptist Church
- Hooff, C. F. May, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-289)
  Road from point in the boundary line between Fairfax and the city of Alexandria...to a junction with the Middle (or Leesburg) Turnpike
- Jones, Robert W. September, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-290)
  Change: County Road from Clifton to Fairfax Station through the lands of R. Jones and the Poor house property (County of Fairfax land)
- Jones, Robert W. September, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-290)
  Change: county road from Clifton to Fairfax Station, through the lands of R. Jones and the Poor house property
- Schreve, W. H. January, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-291)
  Road survey of Schreaves Road leading to Falls Church
- Stone, James E. February, 1896 (Box-folder 8: RP-292)
  Change: Hampton Road, opposite the lands of Fairfax and Marshall
- Hetzel, Margaret September, 1897 (Box-folder 8: RP-293)
  Road from Clifton to Yates Ford Road, through the lands of M. Hetzel, J. T. Pettitt, D. N. Robinson, C. F. Ford, and J. A. Marshall
- Norman, Isaac F. March, 1897 (Box-folder 8: RP-294)
  Change: County road from Fairfax County Road, adjacent to land of N. F. Graham
- Thompson, B. F. November, 1897 (Box-folder 8: RP-295)
  Change: road leading from Sideburn Station to the Fairfax Station Road
- Wiley, Robert August, 1897 (Box-folder 8: RP-296)
  Road from Gunston Road...to crossroads known as Negro Head
- Anbagen, George November, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-297)
  Outlet road in Lee District from Anbagen's farm to the Alexandria Road
- French, W. J. May, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-298)
  County road from a point in the town of Wiehle on the line of the Southern Railway in the Dranesville District...to a point on the Ridge Road
- Gillingham, F. P. January, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-299)
  Discontinue road from A and E Railway Company to the Rolling Road in the Lee District
- Harrover, R. L. October, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-300)
  Road from the lands of William R. Ward to Telegraph Station, through the lands of Mrs. Lee
- Hetzel, Margaret March, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-301)
  Road from Clifton to Mr. Thomas Fenwick's land, intersecting with Colchester Road
- Hetzel, Margaret September, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-302)
  Chapel Street in Clifton Station; extension eastward to Colchester Roll-way
- Koenig, Godfrey July, 1898 (Box-folder 8: RP-303)
  Road from Pohick Road...to the Keene's Mill Road
- Porter, R. S. September, 1898 (Box-folder 9: RP-304)
  Road from the Falls Church and Court House Road to the "Hunter Road"
- Rice, H. D. October, 1898 (Box-folder 9: RP-305)
  Change: road near Bone Mill Ridge over Accotink Run, from Whose Road to the new bridge
- Roley, E. W. December, 1898 (Box-folder 9: RP-306)
  Relocate: County Road from Little River Turnpike to Edgar Scott's Residence
- Utterback, E. W. November, 1898 (Box-folder 9: RP-307)
  Point on county road near Ashton's leading from Little River Turnpike to Centreville to a point on the Warrenton Turnpike
- Bennett, John July, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-308)
  Road from a point on the New Cut Road near Vale Post Office to Ox Road
- Nesbit, W. W. August, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-309)
  Road from Braddock Road to Sagar Avenue near Fairfax Court House
- Stalcup, E. S. September, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-310)
  Establish boundary lines of road leading from Faulkner's shop on Leesburg Turnpike to the residence of Joshua Kirby
- Stalcup, S. F. August, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-311)
  Repair road leading from Ballston to Langley
- Stalcup, S. F. December, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-312)
  County road on the boundary lines of Truitt, Payne, & McNair
- Stuart, William June, 1899 (Box-folder 9: RP-313)
  Open private road to the public; the road at V. W. Lee's to the county road near Stuart's Mill
- Copperhite, Henry January, 1900 (Box-folder 9: RP-313)
  Road from the point on the Braddock Road to a point on the Guinea Road
- Hornbeck, C. W. January, 1900 (Box-folder 9: RP-315)
  Road from Luis Corner to a point on a road from Fairfax to Vienna, opposite or near the road running to Falls Church
- Perl, Herman June, 1900 (Box-folder 9: RP-316)
  Outlet road beginning at the corner of the Wooster tract, along the Van Gorder tract to the Magner Road
- Reynolds, J. T. December, 1901 (Box-folder 9: RP-317)
  Change: public road leading from Jermantown to Oakton
- Triplett, R. C. March, 1901 (Box-folder 9: RP-318)
  Road from the Telegraph Road to Franconia Station
- Bradley, H. E. March, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-319)
  Change: Straighten point on Hampton Road in front of residence of H. E. Bradley through the lands of H. E. Bradley
- Cockrill, H. E. June, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-320)
  Change: Public road from Jermantown to Waples on Millard's Mill
- Cranford, Percy November, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-321)
  Road from the lands of Percy Cranford to Gunston Road, including building a bridge over Keans Creek
- Darby, Rufus H. November, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-322)
  Road from Leesburg Turnpike near Munson's Hill to a point on the public road from Mt. Olivet Church to the Falls Church to the Falls Church and Georgetown Turnpike
- Hill, Keary November, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-323)
  Discontinue a road
- Kuehling, Seth July, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-324)
  Road leading from Lorton Valley Post Office...to the Colchester Public Road
- Laughlin, M. J. September, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-325)
  Change: Road leading from Lewinsville to Chesterbrook
- Milstead, George N. April, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-326)
  Change: Telegraph Road along Accotink Run north of Pohick Church
- Providence District Road Commissioners September, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-327)
  Establish boundary lines of County road leading from Core's corner on the Alexandria Pike to Lewinsville
- March, 1902 (Box-folder RP-328)
  Outlet road from land of Charles H. Smith to Riverside Park Road
- Thompson, B. J. November, 1902 (Box-folder 9: RP-329)